Guide to the Charles Baptie photograph collection, 1917-1995
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 11: People, 1944-1976
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Pictures of miscellaneous people.
  - National Symphony, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Pictures of the National Symphony from 1953. (negatives)
  - Lillian Rogers Parks of the White House, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Pictures of Lillian Rogers Parks of the White House. (negatives)
  - People, 1956, 1957, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Pictures of people. (with negatives)
  - Assistant Secretary Hein Perkins, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Pictures of Assistant Secretary Hein-Perkins. (negatives)
  - Schools, 1954-1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Pictures of people from schools. (negatives)
  - Waves 2nd birthday celebration, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Pictures of people from the WAVES second birthday celebration.
  - American Association of Nursery Men, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
    Portraits and pictures of people with the American Association of Nursery Men. (negatives)
  - American Weekly, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 5-9)
    Portraits and pictures of people with American Weekly. (negatives)
  - Besley, Oliver, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Portraits and pictures of Oliver Besley. (negatives)
  - Fairfax National Bank, 1950s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Portraits and pictures of people with the Fairfax National Bank. (negatives)
  - Geophysical Labs, 1956, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 17, 19-20)
    Pictures of people who work at Geophysical Labs.
  - Hazelton Labs, 1964, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
    People who work at Hazelton Labs.
  - Mount Vernon Research, 1963, 1964, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 7, 9-10, 13)
    People who work at Mount Vernon Research.
  - Texaco, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 3, 6)
    Pictures of people at Texaco stations.
  - Texaco - Art Harold, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
    Pictures of Art Harold.
  - National Memorial Park, 1958-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1, 3, 9, 14)
    People at National Memorial Park. (negatives)
  - Technology, 1950s-1960s (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Pictures of people using technology. (negatives)
  - Leighton, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Pictures of Leighton. (negatives)
  - School Portraits, 1960s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Pictures of school portraits. (with negatives)
  - Ann Wheaton, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Pictures of Ann Wheaton. (negatives)
  - Besley, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Pictures of Besley. (negatives)
  - TGA, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Pictures of people from TGA. (negatvies)
  - Portraits, 1950s-1960s (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Portraits. (negatives)
  - People at work, 1960, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Pictures of people at work.
  - Jayce White Portrait, 1950s-1960s (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Pictures of Jayce White's portraits. (negatives)
  - People at an event, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Pictures of people at an event.
  - Artist painting, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Pictures of an artist painting. (negatives)
  - Thompson wedding, 1960s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Pictures of Thompson wedding. (negatives)
  - Ashworth wedding, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Pictures of Ashworth wedding. (with negatives)
  - Topaz Movie Set, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Photographs of Alfred Hitchcock, John Forsythe, and the film crew.
  - Gift Pack, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Photographs of Richard Nixon and his family in the White House.
  - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Photographs of people. (negatives)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Photographs of people.
  - Photo Album, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Photographs of people doing various jobs.
  - Water [An...] Fire Plug, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Photographs of people around a fire hydrant. (negatives)
  - People, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Photographs of people at a banquet and of notable persons.
  - People, 1950s-1960s (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Prints of various people at a function.
  - Photo Album, 1950s (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Photographs of children.
  - People/Portraits, 1940s (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Wedding Portraits, 1940s-1950s (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Photographs of people at a wedding.
  - Group Portraits, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    Photographs of a Women's Club and Monroe Junior High School.
  - Eisenhower, 1940s (Box 23, Folder 19)
    8x10 inch portrait print and smaller negative.
  - Military men, 1940s (Box 23, Folder 20)
    Photographs of Truman, military officer's homecoming, and portraits.
  - Washington, D.C., Symphony Orchestra, 1950s-1960s (Box 23, Folder 21)
    Photographs of the Washington, D.C., symphony orchestra.
  - Group shots, 1930s (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Photographs of groups.
  - Hostess, 1940s (Box 23, Folder 23)
    Photographs from the Hostess series.
  - Sally Walls, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    Photographs of a woman and man.
  - High School football, 1971, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    Photographs of a high school football team. (negatives)
  - People/Portraits, 1951, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    Photographs of various people. (with negatives)
  - Fairfax High School football, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    Photographs of Fairfax High School football team. (negatives)
  - NMP [Genesa], 1971 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    Photographs of people placing boxes along a grave. (negatives)
  - Desmond Walton, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
    Photographs of Desmond Walton. (negatives)
  - Kennedy and Girl Scouts, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    Photographs of Kennedy with Girl Scouts.
  - Portraits, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 31)
    Portraits signed by the subject.
  - Dolly Madison School, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    Dolly Madison School class photos. (negatives)
  - Homestead, PA, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    Photographs of 100 year celebration in Homestead, PA. (negatives)
  - People, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    Pictures of people at the Little Theatre. (negatives
  - People, 1950s-1960s (Box 26)
    Pictures of people at Alexandria hospital and Mrs. Hunt. (negatives)
  - People, 1950s-1960s (Box 28)
    Pictures of people in houses, Tele Tech, restaurants, and hotels. (negatives)
  - People, 1960s (Box 29)
    Pictures of people involved in the malaria prevention testing and U.S. Generals.
  - People, 1940s (Box 30)
    People in several photos from World War Two.
  - People, 1960s (Box 31)
    People involved in malaria prevention, as well as general people and the Buddy Dean Band.
  - People, 1950s-1960s (Box 32)
    Photographs of people at hotels. (negatives)
  - People, 1940s, 1950s, 1960s (Box 33)
    Pictures of President Truman, a baseball team, a child's haircut, and Adolf Hitler. (with negatives)
  - People, 1961, 1965, 1974 (Box 34)
    Pictures of people within this box.
  - People, 1940s-1950s (Box 35)
    Pictures of people at swim practice, in an officer's club, selling war bonds, and the Helen Jefeson and Army band.
  - People, 1960s (Box 36)
    Photographs of people at the Fairfax Hospital, making bows, and military men.
  - People, 1980s (Box 37)
    Photographs of people on vacation and Charles Baptie at home.
  - People, 1950-1964 (Box 38)
    People campaigning for a hospital, at the Mining Company, Chuck Baptie, the Washington Hebrew Congregation, Tom Lawson, Cowboy Ray Allen, and Harod the Great.
  - People, 1967, 1960s (Box 39)
    Pictures from Woodlawn of Mrs. Udall and a portrait of Mrs. Gibson. Also pictures of people involved in the malaria prevention testing in Ecuador.
  - People, 1960s (Box 40)
    People involved in malaria prevention and testing.
  - People, 1949, 1955, 1965 (Box 41)
    Pictures of Lyndon Johnson, VPI Marines football game with President Truman attending, and President Truman on Air Transport Command plane.
  - People, 1954 (Box 42)
  - People, 1940s, 1960s (Box 43)
    Photographs of President Truman, the Red Cross Canteen, an officer's club reception, Carol Steve, and a Bolivian girl.
  - People, 1945-1946 (Box 44)
    Portraits of General Eisenhower, as well as notable military and political leaders.
  - People, 1949-1952 (Box 45)
    Army time series, Dolly Madison Junior High School group portrait, a Fashion show, and Barry Real Estate.
  - People, 1952-1983 (Box 47)
    President Eisenhower's inaugural, short post club, John Torches group, Secretary of Defense Wilson, National Symphony records, Howard Mitchell, President Eisenhower, President Carter with Pope John Paul II, Denise Hudson, and Symphony volunteers portraits.
  - People, 1960s (Box 48)
    People working with malaria prevention and testing; poster makers; military men; and people relaxing.
  - People, 1960s (Box 50)
    People working with malaria prevention and testing in Ecuador.
  - People, 1960s-1970s (Box 52)
    People at a special locomotive ceremony, Herrich Benmuger kissing a woman, and people at a Texaco station.
  - People, 1955-1958 (Box 53)
    Dr. Ableson Geography, Fairfax Hospital graduation pictures, the National Symphony Orchestra, Mrs. harry Stengle's boy, and General Wainwright.
  - People, 1950s-1960s (Box 54)
    Photographs of Adolf Hitler, Little Theater series, Mrs. Carmey, Gadsby Tavern, and Alexandria Hospital service.
  - People, 1960s (Box 57)
    People on Sully Plantation
  - People, undated (Box 59)
    Picture of General Eisenhower.
  - I watched Eisenhower Campaign, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    People in a car.
  - How to Clean a Dirty City, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    People cleaning; cop writing a ticket to a monkey for littering.
  - He Runs the Show for Ike, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Senator Henry Cabot Lodge and Senator William Knowland.
  - Silliest Statues You Ever Saw, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Tourists looking at statues around Washington, D.C..
  - The Man Ike Trusts with the Cash, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    Secretary of Treasury George Humphrey, Secretary of State John Foster Dulles, and Vice President Richard Nixon.
  - He Makes the Brass See Red, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Prints of Committee Counsel John J. Courtney, Congressman Jack Anderson, and Congressman F. Edward Herbert, Chairman of the Sub Committee on Procurement, examining lighting fixtures; luncheon for former Governor of Louisiana James M. Noe, Admiral Harold Houser, aide to the Secretary of Defense Congressman Edward Herbert, and Admiral Charles Fox, Chief of Navy Materials; Congressman Herbert with his wife and daughter; and secretary Betty Harter, Congressman Herbert and his wife.
  - The Starling Nuisance: He's Driving Everybody Crazy, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    CBS radio newscaster Claude Mahoney.
  - President Portraits, 1952-1972 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Presidents Richard Nixon and his family; Lyndon B. Johnson.
  - People, 1955 (Box 62)
    Pictures of a baby, a man in a costume, a secretary at a desk, a scientist, a woman in a gown, and several portrait sessions.
  - People, 1950s-1960s (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Pictures of Lt. Commander M. Scott Carpenter and his secretary Nancy; President Eisenhower and his pilot.
  - Portfolio, 1960s (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Pictures of people.
  - People, 1950s-1960s (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Group photos, 1950s (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Group photos of people.
  - People, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 68, Folder 8)
    President Harry S. Truman descending airplane staircase.
  - People, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 68, Folder 9)
    President of Capital Airlines Clifford Bell, Capital Airlines airplane.
  - Head shots, 1950s (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Pictures of people's head shots.
  - Military photographs, 1945-1952 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Pictures of military photographs.
  - Miscellaneous Pictures and negatives, 1950s (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Nancy C. Lowe, 1960s (Box 69, Folder 9)
    Pictures of Nancy C. Lowe.
- Series 12: Food, 1950s-1960s
  This series contains photographs and negatives of food from restaurants and Hot Shoppes.
  - Restaurants and Food, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Images of food made in restaurants.
  - Photo Album, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Photographs of food.
  - Food, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Food, 1960s (Box 28)
    Pictures of food from restaurants.
  - Food, 1950s (Box 30)
    Images of food from Hot Shoppes.
  - Food, 1960s (Box 31)
    Images of food.
  - Food, 1950s-1960s (Box 32)
    Images of restaurant food.
  - Food, 1950s-1960s (Box 33)
  - Food, 1950s (Box 35)
    Images of a Thanksgiving dinner.
  - Food, 1950s-1960s (Box 44)
  - Food, 1950s-1960s (Box 47)
    Images of food entitled Statler.
  - Food, 1960s (Box 49)
  - Food, 1960s (Box 52)
    Images of food from the Holiday Inn.
  - Food, 1960s (Box 56)
    Images of food from a series entitled 3 Chefs.
- Series 13: Museum Exhibits, 1952-1970s
  This series contains photographs and negatives of various museum exhibits and artifacts. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary. Artifacts and exhibits include the Star Spangled Banner, dolls, and Smithsonian objects.
  - Star Spangled Banner, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Images of the Star Spangled Banner.
  - American Weekly, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 7, 9)
    Images of a P.O.W. museum exhibit within the American Weekly series. (negatives)
  - Historical Documents, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Negative facsimiles of historical documents. (negatives)
  - Museum Exhibit, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    Photographs of museum exhibits. (negatives)
  - Kodachrome, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Kodachrome from Gallery.
  - Dolls, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Photographs of dolls for a book by Helen Bullard. (negatives)
  - Museum, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    Images of museum artifacts. (negatives)
  - Museum, 1957 (Box 27)
    Photographs of some of the Smithsonian's artifacts.
  - Museum, 1960s-1970s (Box 32)
    Images of rocks from the Smithsonian.
  - Museum, undated (Box 39)
    Images of exhibits from the Smithsonian.
  - Museum, undated (Box 43)
    Images of various artwork, natural, and scientific objects.
  - Museum, undated (Box 45)
    Images of museum artifacts.
  - Museum, 1960s-1970s (Box 47)
    Images taken for a Smithsonian Guide Book.
  - Museum, 1960s-1970s (Box 52)
    Images of Smithsonian exhibits.
  - Museum, 1970s (Box 54)
  - Museum, 1980s (Box 58)
  - Silliest Statues you ever Saw, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Tourists looking at statues around Washington, D.C.
- Series 14: Animals, 1946-1980s
  This series contains photographs and negatives of animals. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary. Animals include monkeys, horses, birds, bees, cattle, dogs, butterflies and animals for scientific testing.
  - Monkeys, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Images of monkeys.
  - American Weekly, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Images of animals in the American Weekly series. (negatives)
  - Hazelton Labs, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 1, 3-5)
    Images of animals used at Hazleton Labs. (negatives)
  - National Memorial Park, 1955-1961 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Pictures of animals at National Memorial Park. (negatives)
  - O'Donovan, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    O'Donovan horse pictures. (negatives)
  - W.L. Clark, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    W.L. Clark horse pictures. (negatives)
  - Photo Album, 1940s-1950s (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Photographs of horseback riding.
  - Nature, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Photographs of birds.
  - Nature, 1970s-1980s (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Photographs of bees.
  - Woman feeding dog treats, 1950s-1960s (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Photographs of a woman feeding treats to a dog.
  - Cattle, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Photographs of cattle.
  - Dog photos, 1940s (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Photographs of dogs.
  - Animals/horses, 1940s (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Photographs of horses.
  - Dog photos, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Dog, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Puppy, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Photographs of a puppy.
  - Animals, 1940s-1950s (Box 25)
    Pictures of animals within this box.
  - Animals, 1960s (Box 31)
    Pictures of cattle.
  - Animals, 1950s-1960s (Box 35)
    Animal photos within the Hostess Cox series.
  - Animals, 1970s-1980s (Box 37)
    Slides of animals.
  - Animals, 1960s (Box 40)
    Pictures of animals within the malaria testing and prevention series.
  - Animals, 1980s (Box 44)
    Pictures of butterflies.
  - Animals, 1947 (Box 45)
    Pictures of Dillard Topsy Setter and of King-Collie, dog of Raynor, Mrs. Aline.
  - Animals, 1948 (Box 47)
    Images from the Turkey Series.
  - Animals, 1980s (Box 48)
    Images of butterflies. (slides)
  - How to Clean a Dirty City, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Police writing a littering ticket to a monkey.
  - Animal, 1946 (Box 62)
    Pictures of a puppy.
  - Cars and animals, 1940s (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Large format prints of animals at the National Zoo, including two hippopotami and a snake.
- Series 15: Technology, 1948-1974
  This series contains photographs and negatives of technology. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary. Images in this series include science labs, computers, a space shuttle, factories, and a camera.
  - American Weekly, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Photographs dealing with technology in the American Weekly series. (negatives)
  - Applied Electro Mechanics, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Images of technology from Applied Electro Mechanics. (negatives)
  - Commonwealth Scientific, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Images of technology from Commonwealth Scientific. (negatives)
  - [Dryomatic], 1956 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Images of technology from Dryomatic. (negatives)
  - Geophysical Labs, 1954, 1956, 1960, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 17-20)
    Images of technology from Geophysical Labs. (negatives)
  - Geophysical Labs, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Images of technology from US Recording. (negatives)
  - Hazelton labs, 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
    Images of technology from Hazelton Labs. (negatives)
  - Mount Vernon Research, 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 7-14)
    Images of technology from Mount Vernon Research. (negatives)
  - Sloan Instruments, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Images of technology from Sloan Instruments. (negatives)
  - Water Authority, 1968, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Images of technology from the Water Authority.
  - Data for Speedlight, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Pictures of data for Speedlight.
  - Technology, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Pictures of technology.
  - Navigation images, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Pictures of navigation images.
  - Technology, 1950s-1960s (Box 26)
    Images of technology in the Alexandria Hospital.
  - Technology, undated (Box 28)
    Images from Tele Tech. (negatives)
  - Technology, 1960s (Box 29)
    Pictures of technology from the malaria prevention and testing series.
  - Technology, 1950s (Box 30)
    Images of technology in a factory.
  - Technology, 1950s (Box 34)
    Photographs from the National Biological Lab.
  - Technology, 1980s (Box 37)
    Images of a space shuttle launch, aircraft and hot air balloons.
  - Technology, undated (Box 41)
    Photographs of the Gas Equipment Center and the ILS Institute.
  - Technology, undated (Box 43)
    Images of technology.
  - Technology, 1948 (Box 45)
    Photographs of the Pepsi Cola Plant.
  - Technology, 1958 (Box 53)
    Dr. Ableson Geography Lab for America Weekly.
  - Technology, 1950s-1960s (Box 56)
    Images of an Editor's house at work. (negatives)
  - Technology, 1970s-1980s (Box 62)
    Large format images of a scientist and of a camera set up.
  - Technology, 1950s-1960s (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Large format images of technology.
  - Computers, 1950s (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Images of computers.
  - Technology, 1950s-1960s (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Series 16: George Mason College, 1959-1976
  This series contains photographs and negatives of George Mason College. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary. Specific subjects include athletic teams, staff members, buildings, campus, students, graduations, George Mason Day, and printed materials.
  - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Photographs of George Mason College.
  - Basketball, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Photographs of George Mason College basketball.
  - Dimitrios Papaconstatopoulus - Physics, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Photographs of Dimitrios Papaconstatopoulus of the Physics Department.
  - Master Plan, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Photographs of George Mason College master plan.
  - Brochures, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Tennis, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Photographs of George Mason College Tennis.
  - Baseball, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Photographs of George Mason College Baseball.
  - Ground Breaking, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Photographs of George Mason College, ground breaking of Thompson Hall.
  - Fenwick Library, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Photographs of George Mason College Fenwick Library.
  - Sign, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Photographs of George Mason College sign.
  - Campus, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Photographs of George Mason College campus.
  - Campus, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Campus, 1973-74 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bailey's Crossroads, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Photographs of George Mason College at Bailey's Crossroads.
  - Athletics, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Photographs of George Mason College athletics.
  - Printed materials, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Photographs of George Mason College Printed Materials.
  - graduations, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Photographs of George Mason College graduations. (with negatives)
  - GMC people, buildings, classes, students, teachers, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Photographs of George Mason College's people, buildings, classes, students, and classrooms.
  - classrooms, aerials, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Photographs of George Mason College's classrooms, aerials.
  - sports, 1969, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Photographs of George Mason College sports.
  - buildings, 1968, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Photographs of George Mason College buildings.
  - portraits, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    George Mason College portraits.
  - Fenwick library, 1964-1972 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    Photographs of Fenwick Library.
  - George Mason Day, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Photographs of George Mason Day.
  - GMC, 1968 (Box 47)
    Images from George Mason College.
  - George Mason College, 1972-1976 (Box 65)
    Miscellaneous images and items from George Mason College.
- Series 17: Vehicles, 1946-1995
  This series contains photographs and negatives of vehicles, such as cars, baby carriage, planes, trains, and ships. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary.
  - Lock at Cumberland, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Image of a vehicle at a lock at Cumberland. (negatives)
  - Hazelton Labs, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Picture of a vehicle at Hazelton Labs. (negatives)
  - Negatives, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Images of vehicles in association with Texaco. (with negatives)
  - Texaco 1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Images of vehicles in association with Texaco.
  - Views of a Baby Carriage, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Pictures of a baby carriage.
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s, 1980s (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Photographs of vehicles.
  - Vehicles, 1950s, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Photographs from Shirlington Photographers, 1946, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Photographs of a locomotive.
  - Train cars, buses, locomotives, 1970s, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Photographs of train cars, buses, locomotives and C and O box cars. (with negatives)
  - transportation, 1940s-1950s (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Photographs of various types of transportation.
  - White Service Postcard Negative, 1950s (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Photographs of White Service vehicle.
  - Car accident, 1970s-1980s (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Photographs of a car accident.
  - Postcards - Vehicles, 1950s-1960s (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Postcards of planes and ships.
  - Vehicles/Transportation, 1930s, 1950s, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 17)